Luying ZENG

94 Carpmael Road, 429828

Phone: 65-85157923 Email: zengluying@gmail.com

<u>PERSONAL SU</u>MMARY

5 years' experience in finance industry and 2.5 years' experience in Asset Management Company. Detailed knowledge in financial market. Self-starting, fast learner and highly adaptable to changes in fast-moving environment; open minded and has strong analytical skills.

EDUCATION

Singapore Management University, Lee Kong Chian School of Business

Jul 2010-June 2011

Masters of Science in Applied Finance

• Awarded Best Student Awards-top 10%, GPA 3.86/4(Dean's List Honor)

Xiamen University, School of Mathematics

Sep 2006-June 2010

BS in Applied Mathematics, minor in Economics

• Xiamen University Best Student Scholarship-top 10%

EXPERIENCE

Midas Asset Management Asia Pte. Ltd.

Dec 2014-Present

Equity Analyst/Assistant Portfolio Manager

- Work in a team to manage long-short equity fund focused on Asia-Pacific area (mainly Greater China area)
- Generate new investment ideas and conduct in-depth fundamental research and analysis of companies and industries
- Understand and monitor key value drivers of companies and industries
- · Conduct broad market and industry analysis to identify investment trends and opportunities
- Recommended over 10 stocks to long over 2 years including Kweichow Moutai, Robam Appliances, New Oriental Education and Anta Sports with over 15% return
- Plan and execute company visits
- Liaise with Midas Head Quarter(Midas International Asset Management Ltd, AUM USD 10 Billion) and provide research support
- Assist in Middle and Back office ad-hoc work and familiar with overall operating process of hedge fund including risk management and compliance

Custom House Fund Service Company

Oct 2011-Nov 2014

Fund Accountant

- Net Asset Value calculations for daily funds
- Analyze the impact of corporate action on portfolios, resolve reconciliation difference and ensure the validity of daily P&L valuation
- Liaise with all parties to the fund in a professional manner (investment managers /advisors, auditors, custodians)
- Evaluate and improve procedures to reduce errors, ensure consistency within department

Standard Chartered Bank, SINGAPORE

Consumer Banking, Marketing Department Intern

- Liaised with internal stakeholders and external vendors to ensure that Priority Banking events communications were executed within timelines
- Assisted supervising in the revamping of communication materials for Priority Banking
- Processed and tracked payment of invoices and ensured accuracy

China Everbright Bank, Xiamen, CHINA

Spring 2010

Corporate Banking Intern

- Familiar with the basic processing of setting up corporate banking accounts
- Communicated with clients on a daily basis and responded to client queries on banking processes

ACTIVITIES

Research Assistant for Professor Mitchell Craig WARACHKA, SMU

Spring 2011

• Searched, compiled and analyzed Trade & Foreign Direct Investment data from CEIC & world bank database

AWARDS

• "Guo Jin Ding, Guo Zhuang Li Hua" Scholarship for academic excellence	2007-2008
• Outstanding Youth League Committee Member, Xiamen University	2007-2008
 Active participant award of School of Mathematics, Xiamen University 	2008-2009

SKILLS

Languages

• English (Fluent), Mandarin (Native), Hokkien (Native)

Others

- Passed all 3 levels of CFA exams
- Proficient with word, Excel (Advanced spreadsheet-based skills and financial modeling skills)
- Proficient with Bloomberg, C programming, Eviews